Class of 1978 Records, 1974-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1978 Records
1974-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1978.
RG 80 UUID:ec38ac31-d9a1-45d8-9812-929e5bd1238a
3 boxes (1.25 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1978.
The Class of 1978 was the hundredth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1978 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1978, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1978 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General n.d. (Box 2271, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1978 (Box 2271, Folder 2)
- Commencement Speaker 1978 (Box 2271, Folder 3)
- Freshman Handbook 1974-1975 (Box 2271, Folder 4)
- Groups 1974-1978 (Box 2271, Folder 5)
- Ivy Day 1978 (Box 2271, Folder 6)
- Last Chapel 1978 (Box 2271, Folder 7)
- Class Letters 2003 (Box 2271, Folder 8)
- Class List 1974 (Box 2271, Folder 9)
- Reunion 1983 (Box 2271, Folder 10)
- Reunion 1988 (Box 2271, Folder 11)
- Reunion 1998 (Box 2271, Folder 12)
- Sophomore Push 1976 (Box 2271, Folder 13)